Used Wonder Cards IDs are the ID of in-game received wonder cards, this is to don't receive wondercards you received before

Wonder Card Slots
There are 12 slots in which you can store a Wonder Card, change the index to navigate through the slots
-Open
Load the Slot's Wonder Card with PikaEdit's Wonder Card Editor
-Change
Load a new Wonder Card already saved in .pgf file format
-Save
Save the Slot's Wonder Card on a .pgf file
-Clear
Remove the Slot's Wonder Card
